welcome to another fee log or blog or
video emotion where do you want to call
it this video is all about some products
some miracle products that I've recently
been introduced you I save miracle I
know that's used a lot when it comes to
talking about products they aren't
miracle products they're just pretty
good and there are some pretty pants
products out there so when you find
something that works and does what it
says it's going to do it's a glorious
thing and we must share that information
I feel very lucky to ever so often have
my hair and makeup done and I used that
time wisely and i grill those experts
until they can't wait to get rid of me
this brilliant product is called
brilliant time after its by bumble and
bumble it is about 19 pounds you can buy
and food so you get your points yes this
was introduced to me by a brilliant hair
stylist called Shelly in LA I was in LA
um she can do magic things with curvy
grips this is such a weird product it's
it's almost like a thickener a wax but
it's not doesn't leave your hair gunky
and waxy it's it's very smooth but I'll
put a bit on I'll just show it's kind of
like a cream and you pop it in your hair
and it gives it just the most incredible
texture without being greasy or heavy
it's fantastic highly recommend that
these next two products are just
beautiful they are Eve long's radiance
perfected tinted moisturizer and the
translucent powder they're quite
expensive you can buy them from space NK
they are both in the region of 50 pounds
I think yeah the foundation the
foundation is 48 pounds and the powders
42 so they are almost
treat but they are worth it the tinted
moisturizer is smooth it goes on with
there's no clogging us know chalking us
it's it's beautiful there isn't a
shimmer on it so you don't you don't get
the kind of sweaty look but it's um is
very moisturizing so you get a youthful
glow not like a cheap shimmer for
knowing the powder this this little
thing is just beautiful I mean it's
almost like a sex toy and not that I
find a sexual bit you know it could be
mistaken born um so here we go check
this house you know fresh air bag a
picket and that's it the powders inside
the base so all you need to do is to
shake it and boom it's ready for action
shine-free quite a lot sweaty mama this
is next product it's nothing short of
genius its buying a company called
sunday riley the product itself is
called good genes and it's brightens
exfoliates plumps lines evens
hyperpigmentation no one has what buyers
increases circulation for instant
radiance it does it it's freakishly good
I worry about what's in it this is
expensive this is a really big treat
this is like a Christmas present type
thing you can buy it from space NK and
get your points or from you can get it
online from cult beauty and that's 85
pounds oh no my brother is fringy I I
get it you know cheaper than that um
that is that is wonderful i use that
just before i'm filming or before going
to a party or some special occasion I
mean Botox eat your heart out that is as
an incredible product this is also
fantastic and it's less than a tenner
look at that everyone
everyone breathe again spine you can get
that from boots for about seven pounds
that I think is the best face sun cream
that you can use every single day I
think that's the best one on the market
it comes in a really nifty left side you
can also use on your body its face and
body its factor 30 it's it's I want miss
sometimes uses some moisturizer I keep
it in my bag everywhere I go so on a day
like this I mean it's October it's
beautiful outside the sun is shining if
you're sitting in the Sun you're going
to get burned you're gonna get red nose
that looks rubbish so I have that with
me just in case we have a beautiful day
so those are my five wonder products for
this month and go forth yeah maybe